Amaze Mkhonto

City of Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa



amazej22@gmail.com



+27812521022



linkedin.com/in/amaze-mkhonto-11ab70164

Summary

I like solving problems and collaborating with other people, software engineering gives me that opportunity and I get to write code. I am well versed in python, Java and Git. I have worked with databases before, I am always excited to uncover and learn new technologies.

Experience

Database Application Developer

APPSolve (Pty) Ltd 2020 - 2020 (less than a year)



Engineering Survey Tutor

University of the Witwatersrand Feb 2018 - Jun 2018 (5 months)

Sillwater Mining Engineer

Sibanye-Stillwater 2017 - 2018 (1 year)

Education



WeThinkCode

Software Engineering Sep 2021 - Dec 2022



Oracle

Business Analysis Mar 2019 - Aug 2019



University of the Witwatersrand

Bachelor of Science - Bsc, Mining Engineering 2013 - Mar 2019



DreamGirls Academy

DreamCode Bootcamp, Digital literacy and coding programme Feb 2019 - Feb 2019

Skills

Git • Underground Mining • GEOVIA Surpac • Geotechnical Engineering • SQL • Web Development • App development • Python (Programming Language)